Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1, Section 5: Boxes 89-110
- Box: 100, Folder: 16 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Item 67: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 7 No. 6, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 23, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 68: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 7 No. 5, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 9, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 69: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 63 No. 26, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 30, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 70: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 7 No. 4, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    February 24, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 71: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 7 No. 3, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    February 10, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 72: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 7 No. 2, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 27, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 73: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 7 No. 1, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 13, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 74: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 63 No. 25, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 16, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 75: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 63 No. 23, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    November 18, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 76: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 7 No. 16, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 10, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 77: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 7 No. 17, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 24, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 78: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 9 No. 18, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 6, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 79: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 9 No. 19, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 80: News Briefs: Public Service Company of Colorado and Subsidiaries Vol. 9 No. 20, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    October 3, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 81: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 23, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 82: Timely Items of Interest No. 102, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 21, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 83: Timely Items of Interest No. 101, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 7, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 84: Timely Items of Interest No. 100, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    Novemeber 23, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 85: Timely Items of Interest No. 99, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    October 26, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 86: Timely Items of Interest No. 94, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 17, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 87: Timely Items of Interest No. 93, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 3, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 88: Timely Items of Interest No. 92, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    July 20, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 89: For Your Informations, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    June 9, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 90: Timely Items of Interest No. 91, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    July 6, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 91: Timely Items of Interest No. 90, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    June 22, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 92: Timely Items of Interest No. 89, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    June8, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 93: Timely Items of Interest No. 88, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    May 25, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 94: Timely Items of Interest No. 87, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    May 11, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 95: Timely Items of Interest No. 86, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    April 27, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 96: Timely Items of Interest No. 85, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    April 13, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 97: Timely Items of Interest No. 84, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 30, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 98: Timely Items of Interest No. 83, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 16, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 99: Timely Items of Interest No. 81, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    February 16, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 100: Timely Items of Interest No. 82, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 2, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 101: Timely Items of Interest No. 80, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    February 2, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 102: Timely Items of Interest No. 79, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    Januray 19, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 103: Timely Items of Interest No. 78, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 5, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 104: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 12, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 105: Timely Items of Interest No. 76, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 8, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 106: Timely Items of Interest No. 75, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Item 107: Timely Items of Interest No. 74, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    November 10, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 108: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    June 30, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 109: Timely Items of Interest No. 73, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    October 27, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 110: Timely Items of Interest No. 72, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    October 13, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 111: Timely Items of Interest No. 71, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 29, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 112: Timely Items of Interest No. 70, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 15, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 113: Timely Items of Interest No. 69, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 1, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 114: Timely Items of Interest No. 68, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 18, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 115: Timely Items of Interest No. 67, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 4, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 116: Timely Items of Interest No. 66, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    July 21, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 117: Timely Items of Interest No. 65, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    July 7, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 118: Timely Items of Interest No. 64, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    June 23, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 119: Timely Items of Interest No. 63, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    June 9, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 120: Timely Items of Interest No. 62, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    May 26, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 121: Timely Items of Interest No. 61, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    May 12, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 122: Timely Items of Interest No. 60, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    April 28, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 123: Timely Items of Interest No. 59, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    April 14, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 124: Timely Items of Interest No. 58, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 31, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 125: Timely Items of Interest No. 57, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 17, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 126: Timely Items of Interest No. 56, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March3, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 127: Timely Items of Interest No. 55, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    February 17, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 128: Timely Items of Interest No. 54, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    February 3, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 129: Timely Items of Interest No. 53, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 20, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 130: Timely Items of Interest No. 52, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 6, 1965. Item is in English.
  - Item 131: Timely Items of Interest No. 51, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 23, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 132: Timely Items of Interest No. 50, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 9, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 133: Timely Items of Interest No. 48, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    November 11, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 134: Timely Items of Interest No. 49, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    November 25, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 135: Timely Items of Interest No. 46, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    October 14, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 136: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    July 10, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 137: Timely Items of Interest No. 45, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 30, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 138: Timely Items of Interest No. 44, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 19, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 139: Timely Items of Interest No. 43, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 2, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 140: Timely Items of Interest No. 40, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    July 22, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 141: Timely Items of Interest No. 39, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    July 8, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 142: Timely Items of Interest No. 38, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    June 24, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 143: Timely Items of Interest No. 37, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    June 10, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 144: Timely Items of Interest No. 36, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    May 27, 964. Item is in English.
  - Item 145: Timely Items of Interest No. 35, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    May 13, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 146: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 25, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 147: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    April 7, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 148: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 17, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 149: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    November 25, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 150: For Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    November 21, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 151: Communications: Attractive Employee Handbook Tells it All, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Item 152: Timely Items of Interest No. 32, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    April 1, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 153: Timely Items of Interest No. 30, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 4, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 154: Timely Items of Interest No. 31, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    March 18, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 155: Timely Items of Interest No. 28, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    February 5, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 156: Timely Items of Interest No. 27, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 22, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 157: Timely Items of Interest No. 26, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    January 8, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 158: Timely Items of Interest No. 34, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    April 29, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 159: Timely Items of Interest No. 23, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    November 27, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 160: Timely Items of Interest No. 24, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 11, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 161: Timely Items of Interest No. 25, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    December 25, 1963. Item is in English.
  - Item 162: Timely Items of Interest No. 23, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Item 163: Timely Items of Interest No. 33, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    April 15, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 164: Timely Items of Interest No. 41, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 5, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 165: Timely Items of Interest No. 42, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 19, 1964. Item is in English.
  - Item 166: Timely Items of Interest No. 96, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    September 14, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 167: Four Your Information, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Item 168: Timely Items of Interest No. 95, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    August 31, 1966. Item is in English.
  - Item 169: Timely Items of Interest No. 98, Publication (Box 100, Folder 16)
    October 12, 1966. Item is in English.
- Box: 100, Folder: 17 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Handbook, Publication (Box 100, Folder 17)
- Box: 100, Folder: 18 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan of The Welfare Plan of Public Service Electric & Gas Company, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
    September 19, 1967. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: In the dark about your future?, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 3: Nuclear Energy: Questions and Answers, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 4: How Nuclear Plants Work, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 5: The Savings with Nuclear Energy, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 6: Recycling Nuclear Fuel, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 7: Employee Relations Review Procedure, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 8: Women in Engineering, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 9: Nuclear Reactor Safety, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 10: Managing Nuclear Waste, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 11: Protecting Nuclear Power Plants, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 12: Insuring Nuclear Risks, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 13: Plutonium in Perspective, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 14: Good Jobs You Never Knew Existed, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 15: The Salem Generating Station, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 16: The Energy Outlook, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 17: Apprentice Training Program, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 18: Hope Creek Generating Station, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 19: Energy and the Environment, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Item 20: PSEG Suggestion Plan Rules, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
    January 2, 1973. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Public Service Electric & Gas Correspondence with Female Employees, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
    August 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The Energy People, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
    Winter 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: At PSE&G Challenges Create Opportunities, Publication (Box 100, Folder 18)
- Box: 100, Folder: 19 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Public Service Research Council, Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Item 2: Public Service Research Council Issue Analysis, Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Item 3: News Release: Study Indicates Unionized Teachers Gain Lower Salary Increases, Strike More, Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
    September 14, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Americans Against Union Controll of Government, Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Item 5: Repport on Union Legislative Activities, Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
    March 27, 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Forewarned! Vol. 6 No. 2, Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
    December 1979. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Forewarned! Vol. 5 No. 10, Publication (Box 100, Folder 19)
    September 1979. Item is in English.
- Box: 100, Folder: 20 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: The Rationale of Labor Management Relations, Publication (Box 100, Folder 20)
    By Herbert Blumer. Item is in English.
- Box: 100, Folder: 21 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Pullman Incorporated, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 2: Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 3: Protection and Security, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 4: Pullman Incorporated: "Portrait at 100", Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 5: The Prudential Insurance Company of America, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 6: Pullman-Standard Employees' Suggestion Program, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 7: Tuition Reimbursement Policy, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 8: Pullman Incorporated: Transportation Equipment Divisions, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 9: Employees' Vacation, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 10: Reimbursement of Relocation Expenses for New Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 11: Reimbursement of Relocation Expenses for Transferred Salaried Employees, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 12: The Manager's Role in Salary Administration, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 13: A Definition of Pullman-Standard Its Goals and Objectives, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 14: Compensation/Salary Administration, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Item 15: Pullman Incorporated Chart, Publication (Box 100, Folder 21)
- Box: 100, Folder: 22 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Special Safety Instructions for Joiners and Trimmers, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
    Revissed June 1, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Special Safety Instructions for Maitenance Pipefitting Operations, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
    Revised June 1, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Special Safety Instructions for Car Steamfitters, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Item 4: Special Safety Rules for Car Electricians, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
    Revised 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Special Safety Instructions for Arc Welding Operators and Electrical Maintenance Men, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
    Revised September 15, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Special Safety Instructions and Information for Women Shop Employees, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
    December 7, 1948. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Special Safety Instructions for Hull Fitters and Grinders, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
    February 23, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Retirement Plans for Employees of Pullman Standard Car Manufacturing Company, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
    Amended January 1, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Modern Pullman-Standard Management Methods: Cost Analysis, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Item 10: Modern Pullman-Standard Management Methods: Handling Equipment, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Item 11: Modern Pullman-Standard Management Methods: Management, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Item 12: Modern Pullman-Standard Management Methods: Handling Men, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Item 13: Modern Pullman-Standard Management Methods: Team Leadership, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Item 14: Modern Pullman-Standard Management Methods: Planning and Organizing, Publication (Box 100, Folder 22)
- Box: 100, Folder: 23 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Business and Industrial Communication from the Viewpoint of the Coporation President, Publication (Box 100, Folder 23)
    By P. E. Lull, F. E. Funk, D. T. Piersol. June 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Toward a Sense of Managerial Purpose, Publication (Box 100, Folder 23)
    July 28, 1966. Item is in English.
- Box: 100, Folder: 24 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: The Organization Behind You and Your Job, Publication (Box 100, Folder 24)
- Box: 101, Folder: 1 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Voluntary Accident Insurance, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Benefit Improvements 1978, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Accident Benefits, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Disability Income, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Dental Care, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Survivors' Benefits, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: You and Quaker, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Quaker Benefits in Brief, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Profit-Sharing and Investment Plan, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Retirement Income, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Benefits in Brief, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Your New Benefits Handbook, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    By Thomas B. Bartel. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Medical Care, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Your Personal Statement of Benefits, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Apprentice Training, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Political Responsibility, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Item 18: Individual Responsibility in Politics, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
    By Donald B. Laurie. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: The Quaker Oats Company Today, Publication (Box 101, Folder 1)
- Box: 101, Folder: 2 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Information for Managers and Supervisors, Publication (Box 101, Folder 2)
- Box: 101, Folder: 3 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Tuition-Aid Plan for Quaker Salaried Employee, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Performance Planning Review, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Flexible Hours Trial, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Collective Bargaining and Labor Contract Administration, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: The Quaker Oats Company Today, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: 100 Years of Looking Forward, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Public Relations Policy and Responsibility, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. June, 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: News about Thee and Me, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Vol 3, No. 1, February/ March 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: News about Thee and Me, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Vol 3, No 2, May/June 1978. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: 80 Years of Looking Forward, Publication (Box 101, Folder 3)
- Box: 101, Folder: 4 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Your Quaker Benefits, Publication (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Drug Abuse Manual, Publication (Box 101, Folder 4)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. April 14, 1972. Item is in English.
- Box: 101, Folder: 5 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Study Guide for Retail Food Store Employees, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Grocery Industry...Past, Present, and Future, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Self-Study Unit 1. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: From the Producer to the Consumer, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Self-Study Unit 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: The Supermarket Today, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Self-Study Unit 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Profit and the Supermarket, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Self-Study Unit 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Supermarket Customer, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Self-Study Unit 5. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: The Grocery Department, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Self-Study Unit 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: The Meat Department, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)
    By The Quaker Oats Company. Self-Study Unit 7. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The Produce Department, Publication (Box 101, Folder 5)